heavy body welcome to this i choose
english' listening practical video
you can use this video to train your
listening and comprehension and ice peak
jcb and join the talk to you about
reading for some people this is a great
topic and 4 other people with my boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy
oh boy
this is the effect the iolite talking
about
zo first lets talk about in the for
great books
first we have difference between
fiction and non-fiction time or fiction
better reach easily reach online fiction
book chair in this category
sambal bawang racing  club the
self-help books biographies
politics of books and many books and those
specifically
that suggest us, I think in particular the is
with you up to or starting to read more than
fiction din fiction but next to my
students wipe box 2 minutes
they usually don't count baby box and then
again line for reading is a great way
to improve your knowledge in your fell
the floor or something
and the drawer people that love reading
selfshot box die cast they want to
improve the wise
okay dominant fiction German idea of
genres white papers
mystery the isle of mystery naples
ein  cm my factory is at the back of the genre
own to christi' in case you before she
actually the best-selling disadvantage is the
ball time
more people pastry napels am any other
other beaks
the reason why like own the christie's
box is that you want i do that keeping the
answer the mystery as i could you no idea
what is going to help with die and the the
book something like barry satisfying further
every he as really like literary
fiction
how it is the fiction and many students
actor everyone high school
usually and highschool students do like
reading books belong with wide web
merry little deeper and more complicated
in
bij also find and thats why i'm really
enjoy reading the great american authors
attest
such as many beautiful john steinbeck
william faulkner
in others liked ernest hemingway in
particular
is one of my father and daughter genres
die interested in is the westhoek summer
of love stories and that the wild west
the politicians hundreds the early my team
van us and also like my mother westerns
stem my figure utterson the chandra
influences are grey blooming more
and come i mccarty setting not many
people like westerns
per four liters super van  andel the many
people prefer fancybox
live curry powder in Game of Thrones
broccoli like them and usually do for
more realistic nails
also a all sleek which you can
who the to learn a language
this is a great way to improve your
English get yourself some interesting
books in English
in my opinion reading your target
language is the best net in for learning
Dutch language
hello there is a gate a bit
cheesybaby material that you can
understand your level european er stupid
try to be the of keybox get your
thoughts and children's books for apple
iphone in french
so out ai by who the dick bit and french
every day and just started an apple
stain pearly easy but also really
interesting for the skyline and him van
at the same time
this is the title learn english us any
recommendations for easy english books
you can know in the comments or other
English longer soundcheck afterwards okay that
will for today
let now in the comments what juffer book
is if see you nexttime
[Music]
[Applause]